http://www.ivysport.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy
Ivysport is committed to protecting your privacy. We collect customer information to improve your overall shopping experience with us. We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining and using this information responsibly. Except as otherwise mentioned below, this privacy policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on our website. By visiting Ivysport, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.
Ivysport Registration
Your personal information and your order history are only available to you if you provide the correct password that you create.
If you forget your password, you can request that it be emailed to your email address. We will not give passwords out over the phone, nor will we email them to a different email address than the one used to register.
Information Sharing
Any personal information you provide to us on our website when you register or update an account, enter a contest or promotion, shop online or request information (i.e. name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card information) is maintained in private files on our secure Web server and our internal systems. We do not share any information with third-parties under any circumstances. Your information is your information.
You should also be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if required to do so by law, governmental request or court order or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with such law, request or court order or to protect the users of our website or the public.
We prefer to keep registered users' personal information accurate and up-to-date. To do this, we provide you with the opportunity to update or modify your personal information, including billing and shipping information, by clicking here.
Links to Other Sites
To enhance your shopping experience, the Ivysport may have links to other sites. Those Web sites will have their own policies on privacy that you may wish to review. Ivysport has no responsibility for these linked Web sites.
Cookies
We use cookies to recognize you and your preferences to make shopping easier and provide you with a customized experience on our website. Cookies are bits of information that we automatically store on your computer if your computer accepts cookies. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information such as your name, address or any financial information on your computer. Ivysport places a unique user ID number on your cookie which allows us to access information that will improve your shopping experience - such as holding items in your shopping cart, accessing your address book, or providing you with customized pages based on your past viewing or purchasing preferences. We also use cookies to track traffic to different parts of the website in order to make improvements and optimize your shopping experience.
If you do not wish to have a cookie on your system, you can set your browser preferences to refuse them. In order to disable cookies, please consult your browser's help section for instructions.
International Orders
If you are visiting Ivysport from a location outside of the U.S., your connection will be through servers located in the U.S. Your orders placed through Ivysport will be accepted, fully processed in and shipped from the U.S. Further, all information you provide will be processed and securely maintained in our Web servers and internal systems located within the U.S.
Email Preferences
If you give us your email address either on the home page or when you register, order, or enter a contest, we will send you emails about Ivysport sales and promotions. We never share your information—including your email—with any outside party!
Child Privacy
Ivysport is concerned about the privacy of young children and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13. Further, Ivysport does not sell products for purchase by children and all children's products we sell are for purchase by adults only.
Secure Ordering
Ivysport believes in providing a safe and secure shopping experience for all of our customers. To that end, Ivysport has implemented security measures to protect the information we collect at our Web site. For example, Ivysport limits the number of employees that have access to the databases that contain personal data, and all Ivysport employees are advised of the importance of confidentiality.
We designed the Ivysport online store to accept orders only from Web browsers that permit communication through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology; for example, 4.0 versions or higher of Netscape Navigator and versions 4.0 or higher of Internet Explorer. This means you'll be unable to inadvertently place an order through an unsecured connection. Browsers that do not meet this requirement will be prevented from navigating the online store section of the Ivysport Web site.
Changes in Policy
As we continue to offer our visitors new and different types of content and services, Ivysport may modify our collection and use practices. Should there be a material change to our policy regarding use of your personal information, we will update this privacy policy statement and advise you of the changes and when they will take effect.
Questions/Contact Us:
If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our privacy practices, please contact us at the following e-mail address, mailing address or telephone number.
By Email: customercare@barnesmith.com
By Phone: (855) 570-8680, Monday-Friday: 8am – 5pm PST U.S. Callers Only (Canada and International callers, please dial (949) 272-8622)
By Writing to us at: Ivysport, Inc., 95 Enterprise, Suite 310, Aliso Viejo, CA 92656
